Patrick Delaney

Web developer

SUMMARY

Dedicated web developer with a bachelor's degree in media and visual arts. Has a wide range of skills from front end to back end development to design and video production. Experienced in high pressure work environments and strict deadlines, as well as quick to learn new technologies.

1729 Boylston Ave, Apt 107 Seattle, WA 98122 (914) 787-0861 pdelaney@outlook.com

https://pat-delaney.github.io/portfolio/

• https://github.com/Pat-Delaney

https://www.linkedin.com/in/delaney-

EDUCATION

University of Washington, Seattle, WA — *Coding Bootcamp Certificate*

October 2022 - May 2023

Studies in: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, progressive web apps, agile methodology, computer science, database theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git

The Evergreen State College, Olympia, WA — Bachelor's of Arts in Media and Visual Arts

September 2017 - June 2021

Studies in: Digital/traditional animation, Video editing, Filmmaking, Radio Documentary, Printmaking, Painting and Writing

PROJECTS

Bargain Bin Electronics — An online marketplace relying on Node.js, Express.js, MySQL and Sequelize.

https://github.com/Pat-Delaney/bargain-bin-electronics

ttps://bargain-bin-electronics.herokuapp.com/

Worldwide News — An online resource to search for news relying on Jquery, Materialize and third party APIs.

https://github.com/Pat-Delaney/worldwidenews

https://pat-delaney.github.io/worldwidenews/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Coding: HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL, NoSQL, Git
- **Microsoft Office**: Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Outlook, etc.
- Adobe CC: Premiere, Photoshop, Aftereffects, Illustrator, etc

EXPERIENCE

Richmark Label, Seattle, WA — *Machine Operator*

July 2022 - PRESENT

- Manage label production from printing to finishing
- Run and maintain Mounvent LB-701/702 UV printers and CEI Boss Digital finishing machines
- Ensure quality control across color, registration and finish

Lantern Press, Seattle, WA — Digital Printing/Direct to Garment Operator

January 2022 - July 2022

- Operate Mimaki JFX200-2513 UV printer and M&R M-link X direct to garment printer to print on shirts, metal and wooden signs and coasters
- Quality control of color, image quality and packaging

Moss Green Inc, Seattle, WA — Screen Printing Assistant

November 2021 - January 2022

- Catch, package and organize screen printed garments
- Weed, pick and print heat-press designs onto garments